<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BitcoinPy on BitcoinPy - Bitcoin Python Resource</title><link>https://bitcoinpy.dev/</link><description>Recent content in BitcoinPy on BitcoinPy - Bitcoin Python Resource</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://bitcoinpy.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Regtest Guide</title><link>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/running-bitcoin/regtest-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/running-bitcoin/regtest-guide/</guid><description>We assume you're running a Bitcoin node on Regtest. In case you're not and you're not sure how to configure your Bitcoin node to run on Regtest have a look at this guide.
Generate address 1bitcoin-cli getnewaddress Generate (mine) blocks bitcoin-cli generatetoaddress &amp;lt;number of blocks&amp;gt; &amp;lt;youraddress&amp;gt;
1bitcoin-cli generatetoaddress 50 bcrt1qywrq947s5yjjn7ye45y9wwh3g093cvec5fl9gn Note that after genering blocks the &amp;quot;mining&amp;quot; rewards can not be usued until they have matured. Rewards are considered matured after 100 confirmations.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/buidl/transactions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/buidl/transactions/</guid><description>Library supports mainnet, testnet and signet and requires internet to work. Despite this section being called Transactions, it will actually show how to generate specific types of Bitcoin addresses and then make a transaction to spend the funds that each specific address type will hold.
Bitcoin doesn't actually have transaction types but has different types of addresses. Each type of address has a different way of &amp;quot;unlocking&amp;quot; its funds.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/python-bitcoinlib/transactions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bitcoinpy.dev/docs/python-bitcoinlib/transactions/</guid><description>Library supports mainnet, testnet and regtest. A PR for signet has been merged but the version that supports it hasn't been released yet. Despite this section being called Transactions, it will actually show how to generate specific types of Bitcoin addresses and then make a transaction to spend the funds that each specific address type will hold.
Bitcoin doesn't actually have transaction types but has different types of addresses.</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://bitcoinpy.dev/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bitcoinpy.dev/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>